Guide to the Stanford Historical Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Biographical Photographs, Series 3
  - Haehl, Harry Lewis (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Hafer, W. Randall (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hager, John M. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hahn, Herbert L. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Hale, Betty (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Haley, Bernard F. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Harvey (and Mrs.) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hall, Harvey Monroe (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hall, Howard Judson (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hall, Lewis Dana (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hamerton-Kelly, Robert (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hamilton, Robert A. "Bones" (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hammond, Owsley B. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hamrdla, G. Robert (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hanna, Junius (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Hanna, Paul R. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Hansen, Hazel (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hansen, Ralph (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hansen, W. W. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hansen, W. W.--Instruments--Fol.1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hansen, W. W.--Instruments--Fol. 2 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Hansen, W. W.--Instruments--Fol. 3 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Hanzlik, Paul J. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Harbaugh, John W. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Harcourt, Robert H. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Harding, Harry (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Hardy, Irene (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Hargadon, Fred (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Harman, Willis W. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Harrell, Thomas W. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Harrelson, William H. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Harriman, Raymond D. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Harris, David (student '60s) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Harris, David W. C. (Faculty) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Harris, Lawrence W. (Harry) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Harris, Pop (bootblack) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Harrison, Benjamin (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Hartley, Flora (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Hastorf, Albert H. (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Hauck, Roland L. (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Haugh, James C. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Hauser, Henry P. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Haven, Martha (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Hay, John (Secretary of State) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Hayes, Elystus L. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Hayes, Rutherford B. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Hays, Alice (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Hazzard, William C. (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Heath, Elsie Shelley (Mrs. Harold) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Heath, Harold (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Heffner, Hubert (son of Hubert C.) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Heffner, Hubert C. (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Helliwell, Robert A. (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Hempl, George (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Henderson, Charles (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Henline, Henry H. (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Henry, Warner W. (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Henshaw, Richard (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Herman, Michael G. (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Herrin, William (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Herrin, William--Family (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Herrington, Marvin (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Hetherington, Clark W. (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Hewlett, Albion Walter (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Hewlett, Flora (Mrs. William R.) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hewlett, William R. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hicks, Herbert S. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hicks, Wesley (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hilgard, Ernest R. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Frank (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hilton, Ronald (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hinsdale, Lester J. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hinsey, Joseph C. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hodges, Charles E. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hodgson, Caspar W.[?] (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hofmann, William (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hofstadter, Robert (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Holbrook, Evans (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Holden, Paul E. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hollander, Mary (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hollister, John J. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Holman, Benjamin (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Holman, Emile (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Holman, Halsted R. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Holsclaw, Florence Mabel (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Holsti, Rudolf (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hood, Wilbur K. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hoopes, Robert (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hoover, Allan (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Groups--Fol. 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Groups--Fol. 2 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Groups--Fol. 3 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Groups--Fol. 4 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hoover. Herbert C.--Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Memorial Service (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Portraits--Fol. 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Portraits--Fol. 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Portraits--Informal (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Hoover, Herbert C.--Mr. & Mrs. (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hoover, Herbert, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Hoover, Lou Henry (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Hoover, Theodore (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Hoover, William G. (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Hopkins, Edward Whiting (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Hopkins, Jeannette Hitchcock (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Hopkins, Mark (and Mrs.) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Hopkins, Timothy--Fol. 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins, Timothy--Fol. 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins, Timothy--Fol. 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins, Timothy--Fol. 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins, Timothy--Fol. 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Horton, Jack K. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hoskins, Leander M. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Houck, George H. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Houser, John David (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Howard, Arthur D. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Howard, Bion B. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Howard, Burt Estes (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Howard, George E. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Howard, Ronald A. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Howell, James E. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Howlett, Elizabeth (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Hubble, Edwin P. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Hudson, William Henry (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Huggins, Richard A. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Huggins, Robert A. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Hukari, Harvey (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Hulme, Edward Maslin (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Hume, (Elsie) May (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Humphrey, Fred (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Hunnecutt, Clarence (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Hunt, Marcie (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Huntington, Collis P. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Huntington, Henry E. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Hussey, William J. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Huston, Charles A. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Huston, H. L. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Huchinson, Enid (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Hutton, Colin O. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Ichihashi, Yamamoto (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Imamura, Fujiko (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Inch, Thomas T. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Ingraham, Irving I. (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Ingraham, Justin (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Ingram, K.C. (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Ireson, W. Grant (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Irwin, Harriet ("Hallie") Hycle (Mrs. Niel) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Irwin, Will H. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Iverson, William (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Jackson, George B. (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Jackson, J. Hugh (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Jacobs, Donald Porter (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Jacobsen, Lydik (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Jacobsen, Lyle (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Jacobson, David S. (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Jagaciak, George (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - James, H. Thomas (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - James, Maud Merrill (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Jaramillo, Josefina (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Jenkins, Alice M. (Mrs. Frank W. Weymouth) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Jenkins, Hubert O. (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Jenkins, Olaf P. (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Jenkins, Oliver Peebles (and Mrs.) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Jennings, Herbert S. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Jensen, Abe (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Johansen, Waldemar (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Milton (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Paul R. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Robert (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, William S. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Johnston, Oliver Martin (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Johnston, Paul C. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Eliot (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Maud (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Jones, William O. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Jonsson, Philip R. and Charlton, Margaret Jonsson (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Jordan, Barbara (DSJ's daughter) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Alaska Fisheries (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Ancestral Home--Birthplace (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Jordan, David Starr--British-American Diplomatic Commission (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Fur Seal Commission (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Greece visit (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Hawaii visits (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Hawaii visits--India Rubber Tree--Fol.1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Hawaii visits--India Rubber Tree--Fol.2 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Ichthyology (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Indiana University (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Japan visits (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Mount Jordan (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--(pre-Stanford)--Fol. 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--(pre-Stanford)--Fol. 2 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.3 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.4 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.7 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.8 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Fol.9 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Informal--Fol. 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Informal--Fol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Informal--Fol. 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Informal--Fol. 4 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Informal--Fol. 5 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Paintings/Drawings (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Sculpture--Fol. 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Sculpture--Fol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Portraits--Sculpture--Fol. 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (Family)--Fol. 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (Family)--Fol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (Family)--Fol. 3 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (non-family)--Fol. 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (non-family)--Fol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (non-family)--Fol. 3 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (non-family)--Fol. 4 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Jordan, David Starr--with others (non-family)--Fol. 5 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Jordan, Edith (Mrs. Nathaniel Gardner) Daughter of Dr. Jordan (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, Eric Knight (son of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Jordan, Harold (son of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, Hiram (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, Hulda Hawley (mother of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, Jessie Knight--Fol. 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, Jessie Knight--Fol. 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, Jessie Knight--Fol. 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Jordan, Jessie Knight--Fol. 4 (Family) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Jordan, Knight Starr (son of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Jordan, Lee Knight (grandson of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, Lucia (sister of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jordan, Mary (sister of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jordan, Rufus--Fol. 1 (brother of Dr. Jordan) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, Rufus--Fol. 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, Susan Bowen (Dr. Jordan's first wife, d. Nov. 15, 1885) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Jorgensen, Henry G. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Judah, Theodore D. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Kailath, Thomas (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Kaplan, Henry S. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Kaplan, John (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Karnes, Thomas (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Kay, Willard (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Kays, William M. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Keady, Michael J. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Keast, George R. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Keesing, Felix (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Keesling, Francis V. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Kefauver, Grayson N. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Kegley, Carl S. (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Kegley, Paul (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Keller, Ralph W. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Kelley, Richard L. (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Kennedy, Anthony M. (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Kennedy, Arthur G. (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Kennedy, David M. (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Kennedy, Donald--President--Fol. 1 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Kennedy, Donald--President--Fol. 2 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Kennedy, Donald--Inauguration (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Kennedy, Jeanne D. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Kennedy, Martin H. (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Keohane, Nannerl (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Keohane, Robert (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Keough, William T. (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Kerensky, Alexander (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Killefer, Tom (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Kiler, Leslie (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Kimball, Edwin B. (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Kimball, Gordon Eugene (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Kimball, William R. (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A. (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Kinney, Wendell H. (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Kirk, Dudley (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Kirkman, Hadley (and Mrs.) (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Kirkpatrick, Paul (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Kirkwood, Daniel (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Kirkwood, Marion Rice (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Kirtland, John Copeland, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Kishimoto, Hideo (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Kistler, Roy E. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Klotz, Sergius (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Knapp, Maud L. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Knoch, Charlotte A. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Knoche, Herman (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Knoles, George Harmon (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Knox, Fannie (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Knox, Newton B. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kocher, George S. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Koenig, Frederick O. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Kohfeldt, Mary Lou (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Kornberg, Arthur (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Krauskopf, Konrad B. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Krehbiel, Edward B (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kreps, Theodore T. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Kriehn, George (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Kriss, Joseph P. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Krauskopf, Konrad B. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Kroeger, Arthur (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Kropp, Donald J. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Krough, Edward "Ted" (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Laird, John A., Jr. (Jack) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lamonaco, Neal W. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Lane, Levi Cooper (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Lane, Melvin B. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Laney, Jack H. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Lapham, Roger D. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - La Piere, Richard T. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Larson, Cedric. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Larson, Jolene (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Larson, Robert E. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Lathrop, Henry Burrows (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Latimer, F. P. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Lauritzen, John B. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Lawrence, Ernest (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Lawson, James R. (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Leavitt, Harold J. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Lebacqz, Jean V. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Lederberg, Joshua (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Lee, Horace B. ("H.B.") (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Lee, Lamar (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Lee, Russel V. (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Lehman, Arnold J. (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Leib, Samuel F. (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Leighton, Joseph A. (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Leighton, Philip A. (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Lenox, Lionel R. (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Leppert, George (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Lesley, Everett P. (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Letourneau, Lowell S. (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Levin, Peter J. (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Levorsen, A. Irving (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Lewis, J. Roger (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Lewis, Robert S. (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Liddle, Elise (Mrs. George) (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Liebendorfer, Don (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Liggett, James B. (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Linsley, Ray K. (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Little, Charles (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Littleboy, Jeffery I. (and Mrs.) (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Littler, Robert (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Livingston, Lawrence Jr. (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Long, Lucille (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Loofbourow, Robert L. (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Loomis, Frederick C. (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Loomis, George (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Loper, Robert (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Loring, Hubert S. (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Loud, Henry Lawrence (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Love, Ernest A. (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Low, John Stewart (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Liljenwall, Theodore G. (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Luce, Henry R. (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Luck, J. Murray (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Luebke, William R. (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Luisetti, Angelo "Hank" (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Lundborg, Louis B. (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Lusignan, Joseph (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Lutz, Ralph H. (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Lyman, Richard W.--Fol. 1 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Lyman, Richard W.--Fol. 2 (Presentation of Sterling Professorship) (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Lyman, Richard W. (and Mrs.) (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Lyon, Dorsey A. (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - MacConnell, James O. (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - MacGintie, George E. (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Mackey, Len (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mackintosh, Kenneth (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MacLeish, Archibald D. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mallett, Robert M. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Malmquist, Lincoln (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Maloney, Harry W. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Maloy, Jeff L. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Manning, Bayliss (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Manning, Laurence A. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Manning, William A. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Manwaring, Wilfred H. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marble, John E. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Margolin, Alvin R. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Marks, Leonard (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Marston, John M. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Martin, Boyd (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Martin, Ernest Gale (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Martin, Ernest Whitney (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Martin, Lillien J. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Martinelli, Alberto (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Marton, Ladislaus Lazlo (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Martzloff, Thomas H. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Marx, Charles David--Fol. 1 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Marx, Charles David--Fol. 2 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Marx, Guido H. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Mason, Jeffrey L. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Masters, Alfred R. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Matzke, John E. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - May, Ernest R. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Mayer, Quinn B. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Mazour, Anatole G. (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - McBain, James W. (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - McClelland, John (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - McClintock, Miller (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - McColl, William "Bill" (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - McCoy, Bowen H. (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - McCracken, Mary Isabel (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - McCurdy, Richard C. (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - McDaniel, George W. (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - McDaniels, John H. (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - McDonald, E. B. (Sam) (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - McDonnell, Robert H. (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - McDowell, Carl E. (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - McDowell, John Ezra (and Mrs.) (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - McElroy, Floyd L. (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - McFadden, Duncan I. (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - McFarland, Frank Mace (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - McGhie, Farrell (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - McGilvary, Evander Bradley (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - McGuire, Thomas G. (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - McKee, Downing (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - McKee, Paul B. (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - McKenory, Ramona (Mrs. Handley Murray) (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - McLaine, William L. (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - McMurphy, James I. W. (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - McNeil, Wilber C. (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - McNemar, Quinn (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Means, John H. (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Mears, Eliot (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Meindel, James D. (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Mellinkoff, Sherman (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Mendelowitz, Daniel M. (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Meritt, Herbert D. (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Merrill, Fred H. (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Merrill, Samuel (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Merryman, John Henry (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Mestre, Harold (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Meyer, Arthur W. (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Meyer, J. Henry (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Meyer, Margaret (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Meyers, Charles J. (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Michaels, Frederick Dewey (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Michotte, Albert E. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Middlebrook, Diane W. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mielke, Frederick W., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Milbank, Norman (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Miles, Catherine Cox (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Miles, Walter R. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Arjay (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Arthur L. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Miller, Earl E. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Miller, Guy C. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Miller, John C. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Walter (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Miller, William F. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Miller, William H. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Milliken, Robert A. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Minto, Robert M. "Rabb" (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Mirrielees, Edith R. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell, Dean (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Mitchell, J. Pearce (and Lydia) (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Moffat, Robert (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Moffitt, A. Hubbard, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Mollinkopf, John (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Molotov (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Momaday, N. Scott (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Moore, Arthur Russell (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Moore, Bryan S. "Dinty" (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Morell, George F. (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Moreno, Halcott G. (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Morgan, Bayard Q. (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Morgan, Mr. and Mrs. F.E. (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Morgan, Lee (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Morris, Samuel B. (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Morrison, Stanley (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Morshead, Stuart W. (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Moscrip, James H. "Monk" (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Moser, Charles (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel--Fol. #1 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel--Fol. #2 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel--Fol. #3 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Mosher, Francis W., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Mosher, Harry S. (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Mothershead, John L., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Moultin, Robert H., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Muellhaupt, Mary S. (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Murphy, Daniel W. (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Murphy, James J. (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Murphy, Thomas J. (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Murray, Augustus T. (and family) (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Murray, Francis K. (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Murray, Frederic S. (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Murray, Minerva (Mrs. Leland R. Skelton) (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Murray, (Robert) Lindley (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Muybridge, Eadweard (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Myers, Henry C. (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Naftzger, Roy (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Nanney, Herbert (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Napier, B. Davie (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Narver, David L. (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Nash, Herbert C. (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Neely, Guy R. (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Neikirk, W. Thom (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Nelson, Lyle M. (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Nelson, Wilbur A. (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Newell, Henry (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Newell, Tom (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Newhall, William Mayo (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Newsom, John F. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Nibley, Joel (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Nichols, Jesse E. (Mrs.) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Niebel, H. Lee (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Niel, Cornelius van (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Nielsen, Oswald (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Nilan, Roxanne (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Niles, Alfred S. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Nixon, John E. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Nogales, Luis (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Nolan, Lloyd B. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Nold, Ellen (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - North, Robert C. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Northway, William H. (Box 19, Folder 18)